Marc SooHoo

Student at Design Tech High School + Experienced Intern

1620 Hull Drive San Carlos, CA 94070, USA

+1-650-832-8004 msoohoo701@gmail.com

About Me

I am 16 years old and a junior (11th grade) in Design Tech High School, a public charter, STEM project based high school with heavy emphasis on design thinking.

I am a driven individual who strives for delivering the best outcome. Adaptable to most situations and problems given, and taking responsibility when working, I also keep communication as a top priority.

My interest includes STEM subjects, particularly math, science, robotics and engineering (electrical, mechanical and aerospace).

Experience

Intern - Mingcha HK

June 2023 - July 2023, Hong Kong

- Event Planning
- Event set up
- Inventory
- Assemble product packages

Intern - Women's Coaching Alliance

October 2022 - November 2022, Burlingame, CA

- Learned valuable skills pertaining to organizing documents and emails.
- Provided and researched sponsorship information to the director
- Obtained a letter of recommendation for excellent responsibility and adaptability

Intern - Bess Ho (Tech startup advisor, angel investor, former UC Santa Cruz extension faculty)

July 2022 - September 2022, San Carlos, CA

- Spearheaded a project which involved setting up a workshop of 3D printers
- Received a project brief to create sets of 3D printed stamps for embossing logos on branded ceramic plates and pots.
- Created a satisfactory set of products for the client
- Exhibited a proficiency in quick learning and adaptability
- Received a letter of recommendation for performance

Extracurricular Activities

Martial Arts - blue belt - has been taking martial arts for 10 years

- ASME student member
- Finance Director at High School Aviation club
- School electronics repair and rebuild

Skills

- Google Work Suites (Docs, Sheets, Slides)
- 3D printing and rapid prototyping
- CAD (SketchUp and TinkerCAD)
- Database and CRM management

Education

Design Tech High School

September 2020 - July 2024, Redwood Shores, CA

- Currently a junior in Design Tech High School, a STEM focused, design thinking, project -based charter school preparing students to excel in STEM fields and beyond.
- GPA 3.7 (A-); full GPA is 4.0 (A)
- Expected graduation May 2024

(References on next page)

References

Bess Ho, bess.ho@gmail.com

Pam Baker, pam@womenscoachingalliance.com